Here's the train I got on.
Whoo!
Whoo! Here it comes!
This is where I got here safely.
Just keep going, just keep going.
A little scary.
Hi, I'm Meguki Nakajima from Sakurazaka 46!
Yay!
So...
I'm here at Tenjin station in Fukuoka.
It's the day after the Horse Tour in Fukuoka Park.
I'm actually a little bit nervous, because I got to be on such a sparkling stage yesterday...
I'm enjoying my hometown with a bit of looseness.
Today, I'm here at Tenjin station, Nishitetsu station.
Thank you very much for watching.
Today, I'm going to take a trip by myself on Nishitetsu train, which I've been using since I was a student here in Nishitetsu.
I'm going on a trip by myself.
I used to drink tapioca here with my friends when I was in high school.
And this is my companion for today's trip.
This is the packet I'm hanging right now.
This is a packet that I thought of.
It's a packet of goods, and I put my own photo in it.
The reason why I'm doing this is because people who support me often ask me to bring my goods with me on my trip to Fukuoka.
I thought I'd try to imitate them, so today I'm going to put my picture in the packet.
I thought I'd try to imitate them, so today I'm going to double-use them!
Cute!
The candle is freaking out!
Broadcasting in the car
Well, we've arrived at Rasaif!
Great train, the train is talking...
We're in Rasaif!
We're on the train.
It's like this.
For three years in high school and even after graduation.
I used to take the Nishitetsu train to my part-time job.
I used to take the train a lot.
This is the train I took.
I'm walking in Razaifu.
This is the place where we filmed
I came here to shoot the vlog for the unveiling of Sakurazaka 46, didn't I?
I'm still not used to taking pictures with a camera like this.
I'm not used to taking pictures with a camera like this, so it hasn't changed a bit from a year ago.
But it's the day after the show.
Maybe some of you might be fans.
I'm going to take this and join them.
I'm standing in line at the ice cream shop.
I'm so confused.
The sweet and tasty strawberry one looks so good!
But they also have cherry flavor!
There's no choice but to choose the cherry flavor!
It's so hard to decide!
It'll be my turn soon.
Thank you very much.
Bon appétit!
I could drink it with sweet strawberry
Hey, even though it has the word "sakura" in it...
I ended up with strawberry.
I love strawberries, don't you?
Cherry blossoms are nice, though.
I just started taking pictures.
Oh, no!
You didn't get it? I don't know.
You said it was super delicious.
It's super delicious.
It's so good!
I just came to check out the restaurant we vlogged at.
It's called Tenzan.
They also have strawberry daifuku!
Yomechan here loves the inside!
It's really beautiful! The plum blossoms are blooming too!
That's why.
Can you see the plum blossoms? Let's go a little further this way.
Plum blossoms!
Here we are.
I think I'll go in now.
It looks like they've finished construction on the main shrine.
It's so magnificent!
It's really great, really great.
This is the first time I've been here since it looked like this.
I'm so happy!
Pray?
Let's pray.
I prayed for the success of this tour.
He's the god of academics.
I always ask him to watch over me
I always ask him to watch over me so that I don't get hurt.
I came to the bench where I used to sit in the vlog.
I don't know how to take a video or something.
I remember taking a video here alone, quietly worrying about how to take a video.
Now that I've had a chance to explore Dazaef a little bit
I'd like to get on the train again.
I'll buy a ticket.
I want to get off at Miyanojin station.
470 yen!
Oh, I'm through the ticket gate!
First of all, I'm going to be there for 2 days and 1 day.
Oh, the train is leaving already!
I wonder if I can make it in time.
We've arrived at Nishitetsu Miyanojin station!
I was going to go to Kurume.
But I got off the train a little before.
Chikugo River is nearby.
I'm thinking of going to see it.
The scenery is all at once again
Oh! There's some kind of tourist information map!
I knew it! It says "Kurume Ramen" or something like that!
Near the pool
By the big river!
Let's go see the big river.
Shikoku River
Get off at Miyanojin station
Walk
Just a short walk
I was walking in a huff...
Hurrah!
So cute! Is it the biggest one you've ever seen? I don't know if it's the biggest, so I'm not gonna tell you.
Oh! There's a great train!
Wow!
Oh, my gosh!
Wow! Here it comes!
Wow!
Oh!
Hello! Train!
I think this kind of scenery suits me.
It makes me feel at home.
I just wanted to say that today was the next day of the Fukuoka leg of the tour.
I was on the Fukuoka leg of the tour until yesterday.
I'd like to talk a little about the concert.
I'd like to talk a little bit about the live show and the peaceful scenery.
I've been saying that my dream is to stand in Fukuoka Dome in the future.
Marine Messe was also a dream of mine, so I was super happy to be there.
I was super happy.
I should have said that at the concert.
But I was so happy that I probably talked too much during the Fukuoka MC.
I probably talked too much.
Also, I had a friend from my hometown
My local friends came to Fukuoka Park!
I'm really looking at all the pink, pink, pink penlights.
I was looking at all the pink, pink, pink penlights. Friends? Sometimes I wonder if they're my friends.
I was really surprised.
Especially my friends from college were so surprised because I auditioned for the show and suddenly jumped into this world.
I apologized for suddenly jumping into this world.
But they were so supportive.
They took a picture of me with my picture.
It was like...
I was so happy that they came to support my live performance.
I was so happy that they decided to have an additional show at Tokyo Dome.
When it was announced that it was going to be at Tokyo Dome, one of the senpai said something like, "Thank you for the third term students.
I told him that it was nothing like that.
But I thought that things had changed a little from a year ago when I was just looking at my seniors' backs.
I was very happy to hear that.
I feel that I'm getting used to working with the seniors more and more.
And the third-term students are third-term students.
I also feel that the relationship with them is changing a little bit.
I don't think it's right to say that the relationship is changing.
It's a little bit
deeper and deeper
It's getting deeper.
Sometimes I'm glad to hear that.
We're so close that it's a little scary.
Everyone.
We talked about the Shikoku River.
I'm thinking of going to Kurume.
We've passed it.
Scary.
Wow!
We've arrived at Nishitetsu Kurume Station.
Kurume is not my hometown, so this is my first time here.
I've heard Kurume Ramen is delicious!
I'm looking for a Kurume Ramen shop today
I'm looking for a Kurume Ramen shop and want to eat something!
I want to enjoy the local taste of Fukuoka!
See you soon!
There is a ramen shop!
This way!
Ramen
Menshi-san
Is this intonation correct?
ramen
It is written "Kurumi Ramen".
It's a meal ticket type.
Let's see...
I'll have this "light" ramen.
I'll have the "Odo Ramen".
Ta-da!
It smells really good!
Bon appétit!
I'm so excited!
I chose one side!
It's one-sided rice.
Looks delicious!
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
Delicious! I wonder if she's eating ramen now.
If I eat ramen like this too...
You may think I'm just pushing ramen in three mouthfuls, but
Hakata ramen is really good!
Delicious!
I finished it! In the blink of an eye!
Well, I finished it in no time at all!
I forgot to take a picture of it before I ate it.
That was delicious, Yuzu!
Thanks for the food!
I had ramen and whip.
It was delicious!
Yes, I went to a little place near Kurume station
I had ramen, Kurume ramen.
Sorry!
It was delicious, but...
I just wandered around a little bit.
I went to have a meal.
Um...
We arrived at Kurume City Central Park.
It looks like this.
It's a park.
I like it better this way, wind.
The ramen was really good.
I was really impressed, it was tonkotsu (pork bone) ramen!
I was so happy to be able to eat it.
The wind was amazing!
How was Yuzu's solo trip on the West Railways?
How was it?
There is a reason why I decided
There's a reason.
I used to use the Nishitetsu Line, so I was a user.
I used to use it, so I was a user.
I thought it was nostalgic
I wanted to try it.
I didn't use it all day long.
Today, from Tenjin to Dajaef to
to Kurume
Um, as I was moving
Ah, wan-chan! Moving from one place to another
I enjoyed Fukuoka!
So, if you like this video, please click the "Good" button.
If you liked this video, please click the Good button!
And please subscribe to our channel!
See you soon!
Bye bye!